apsira.com 2013-04-03

# Privacy Policies

| 

## Registration

You may provide us with certain information such as your name, email address, postal address when registering for certain services such as Online Registration, Contests. This information will primarily be used for the purpose of providing personalization and verification.

## Feedback

Our site's feedback form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code etc ).

We use customer contact information from the feedback form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitors' experience at our site, showing them the content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may optional out of receiving future mailings; by sending us an e-mail.

## IP Addresses

We use IP addresses for statistical and system administration purposes. IP addresses are anonymously logged to track a users session. We do not link IP addresses with any personally identifiable information. This means that a users session will be logged but that user will remain anonymous to us. We can and will use IP address to identify a user when necessary to enforce our terms of service or protect our site, network, advertisers or users.

## Cookies

Apsira uses session cookies to prevent banner network and affiliate system abuse and cheating. This cookie does not contain any personally identifiable information about users.

Apsira does not require a user to accept or use browser cookies. Most web browsers will allow you the option to reject cookies or to choose which cookies to accept.

## Contact Information

We collect contact information (like your name, address, telephone number, email address and URL) through various registration forms, surveys etc.

This information is used to provide you with services that you requested (like submitting your Queries to our search engine, joining our link exchange service, or if you order products and services), contact you when necessary, or to send you additional information regarding Apsira or selected reputable partners and affiliates.

## Notification of Changes to the Privacy Policy:

Our privacy policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. If at some point in the future, Apsira changes the usage practices that affect any of your personally identifiable information, we will notify you by email of the changes.

## Security of Information

Apsira shall store all the user information securely, as per the standard guidelines set by the Systems Dept. of Apsira and such user information are not shared with any third parties, except for reasons that require and as necessary to fulfill a transaction the user has requested for, or unless otherwise the user gives Apsira the permission to do so. Apsira may also share such information in response to any legal process, as may be necessitated.

If you have any questions about privacy policy of the APSIRA Web Portal please contact Us

**Our Address** :  
Apsira.com  
C/o Jadian Technologies,  
10, Lal Mohamed 3rd Cross Street,  
Chepauk, Chennai - 600 005.  
Phone: 91-44-2855 2042  
Fax: 91-44-2855 2042

Or write to us at [webmaster@apsira.com](mailto:webmaster@apsira.com)

|
